<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<facts>
  <plant1>
	<set1>
		<question>What are the two substances produced by Aloe Vera that are used for medicinal purposes?</question>
		<answer>Answer: Gel and Latex. Gel is the clear, jelly-like substance found in the inner part of the aloe plant leaf. Latex comes from just under the plant’s skin and is yellow in color.</answer>
	</set1>
	<set2>
		<question>It is believed that Cleopatra applied Aloe Vera's gel to her body as part of her beauty regimen. True or false?</question>
		<answer>True! Studies show that the gel can penetrate three epidermal layers of the skin. Aloe Vera gel may improve absorption of other botanical herbs and vitamins.</answer>
	</set2>
	<set3>
		<question>Aloe Vera is made up of 0.5 percent solid portions that contain active nutrients. What is the remaining 99.5 percent?</question>
		<answer>Answer: Water! They're mostly water, just like us.</answer>
	</set3>
	
  </plant1>
  <plant2>
	<set1>
		<question>How many common names does Kalanchoe pinnata have?</question>
		<answer>Answer: It is known for at least 27 common names throughout the world. Wow, that's a lot of names!</answer>
	</set1>
	<set2>
		<question>Which parts of this plant can be used for medicinal purposes?</question>
		<answer>Answer: All of it! Not a single thing goes to waste.</answer>
	</set2>
	<set3>
		<question>How tall can this plant grow?</question>
		<answer>Kalanchoe pinnata can grow from 0.4m all the way up to 1.4m in height. That's even taller than some people!</answer>
	</set3>
	
  </plant2>
  <plant3>
	<set1>
		<question>What color are Lagundi flowers?</question>
		<answer>Answer: They bloom in colors of blue to lavender.</answer>
	</set1>
	<set2>
		<question>In what regions are Lagundi commonly found?</question>
		<answer>They are commonly found in Asia, particularly in Southeast Asia. That's where we live!</answer>
	</set2>
	<set3>
		<question>Which parts of Lagundi can the most health benefits be extracted from?</question>
		<answer>Answer: The leaves and the roots.</answer>
	</set3>
	
  </plant3>
  <plant4>
	<set1>
		<question>It is said that when Oregano is in bloom, it grows beautiful purple or pink flowers that are also edible. True or false?</question>
		<answer>True! We know its beautiful, but is it tasty?.</answer>
	</set1>
	<set2>
		<question>What was it called as it grew popular in America after soldiers returned from World War II?</question>
		<answer>Answer: Pizza herb! The soldiers craved for pizza after returning from the Mediterraneans, hence the name. </answer>
	</set2>
	<set3>
		<question>There are over 40 varieties of Oregano. The most common one being Oregano vulgare also known as ________</question>
		<answer>Answer: Spanish Thyme.</answer>
	</set3>
	
  </plant4>
  <plant5>
	<set1>
		<question>How tall can a Sambong plant grow?</question>
		<answer>Answer: It can grow up to 4 meters in height!</answer>
	</set1>
	<set2>
		<question>Can Sambong be eaten?</question>
		<answer>Answer: Yes! The leaves are actually used as a flavoring ingredient.</answer>
	</set2>
	<set3>
		<question>Where can Sambong be found?</question>
		<answer>Answer: It is widely distributed in Eastern and Southeastern Asia.</answer>
	</set3>
	
  </plant5>
  <plant6>
	<set1>
		<question>Why is Serenoa repens commonly known as Saw Palmetto?</question>
		<answer>As its name implies, the plant looks like an actual saw with spikes running down its edges. Cool!</answer>
	</set1>
	<set2>
		<question>Saw Palmetto is indigenous to what place?</question>
		<answer>Answer: They grow in the coastal regions of southern United States like Florida.</answer>
	</set2>
	<set3>
		<question>Saw Palmetto is directly edible. True or false?</question>
		<answer>True! Humans have been using saw palmetto as a food source for a long time too! Even before Columbus landed, different groups of people from Native Americans to the Spanish have used it for its nutritional value.</answer>
	</set3>
	
	
  </plant6>
  <plant7>
	<set1>
		<question>Why is Rauvolfia serpentina called snakeroot? </question>
		<answer>Answer: The name snakeroot came from the belief that a root poultice was a cure for snakebites.</answer>
	</set1>
	<set2>
		<question>What properties are Indian Snakeroot known to possess which gives it medicinal value?</question>
		<answer>Indian Snakeroot has been used for centuries in India. It possesses sedative and hypnotic properties. It is used to aid in treating mental illnesses.</answer>
	</set2>
	<set3>
		<question>Indian Snakeroot is known to bloom flowers during winter months. What color are they?</question>
		<answer>Answer: Its are pink or white in color and form in clumps. Fruits are small drupes which are green initially and turn purple black when ripened.</answer>
	</set3>
	
  </plant7>
  
</facts>